<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Youkraine</string>
    <string name="example_autocompletetextview">Example showing AutoCompleteTextView</string>
    <string name="Daylylife" />
    <string name="Essentials" />
    <string name="link_EducationDiplomOnlineApp" translatable="false">https://ufm.dk/en/education/recognition-and-transparency/get-assessment/form-standard</string>
    <string name="link_EducationDiplomPDFApp" translatable="false">https://ufm.dk/en/education/recognition-and-transparency/get-assessment/form-standard/pdf-application</string>
    <string name="link_EducationOptions" translatable="false">https://ufm.dk/en/refugees-from-ukraine-welcome/higher-education-options-in-denmark-if-you-are-a-refugee-from-ukraine</string>
    <string name="link_EducationSUInfo" translatable="false">https://www.su.dk/english/</string>
    <string name="link_EducationSUConditions" translatable="false">https://www.su.dk/english/su-as-a-foreign-citizen/equal-status-according-to-danish-rules/you-fall-within-section-2-2-or-3-of-the-act-on-integration-of-aliens-in-denmark/</string>
    <string-array name="RegionSpinner_values">
        <item>Midtjylland</item>
        <item>Nordjylland</item>
        <item>Syddanmark</item>
        <item>Sjælland</item>
        <item>Hovedstaden</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">LoginActivity</string>
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome !"</string>
    <string name="invalid_username">Not a valid username</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Password must be >5 characters</string>
    <string name="login_failed">"Login failed"</string>
    <string name="title_activity_landing">LandingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- EDUCATION STRINGS -->
    <string name="educationHomeToolbarText">Education</string>
    <string name="educationHomeBold1">Diplom verification</string>
    <string name="educationHomeBold2">Education options</string>
    <string name="educationHomeBold3" translatable="false">SU</string>
    <string name="educationHomeText1">Here is information for you If you are a refugee from Ukraine since 24th of February and consider studying in Denmark.  On this page you can get information about:</string>
    <string name="educationHomeText2">how and if you can verify your current education</string>
    <string name="educationHomeText3">what are your options for studying in Denmark</string>
    <string name="educationHomeText4">how to check if you can receive SU while studying in Denmark</string>
    <string name="educationHomeBtn1">Diplom verification</string>
    <string name="educationHomeBtn2">Education Options</string>
    <string name="educationHomeBtn3" translatable="false">SU</string>

    <string name="educationDiplomToolbarText">Diplom verification</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomBold1">Online application:</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomBold2">PDF application form:</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomText1">You can varify your diplom to be able to study or work in Denmark within your profession.  Your assessment can be applied either online or in PDF format.</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomBtn1">What are the the required document to be included in the application?</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomBtn2">How do I fill in the online application?</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomBtn3">How do I fill in the PDF application?</string>

    <string name="educationOptionsToolbarText">Education options</string>
    <string name="educationOptionsText1">You can continue studying your higher education programme in Denmark or begin a new higher education in Denmark.  To do this you can:</string>
    <string name="educationOptionsText2">1. apply for a transfer from your Ukrainian higher education programme to a Danish higher education programme or</string>
    <string name="educationOptionsText3">2. apply for admission to a new full time higher education programme in Denmark.</string>
    <string name="educationOptionsText4">More information about education options and relevant links can be found here:</string>
    <string name="educationOptionsBtn1">How do I apply for a transfer?</string>
    <string name="educationOptionsBtn2">How do I apply for admission?</string>

    <string name="educationSUToolbarText" translatable="false">SU</string>
    <string name="educationSUBold1">What is SU and SU-loan?</string>
    <string name="educationSUBold2">How do I apply for SU or SU-loan?</string>
    <string name="educationSUBold3">Speical conditions for Ukrainian refugees</string>
    <string name="educationSUText1">“SU” and “SU-loan” is State Educational Grant and Loan Scheme. Society lends students a helping hand in covering living costs for a great variety of courses and studies.</string>
    <string name="educationSUText2">If you want to apply for SU or a SU-loan, you must apply for SU in minSU. Log on to minSU from a computer insted af a mobile device - they do not recieve all applications completed via a mobile device. For this you need to log in with your MitID.   If you are not sure how to use MitID, check out the page within the Essentials category, or click this button:</string>
    <string name="educationSUText3">More information here:</string>
    <string name="educationSUText4">If you are a refugee from Ukraine, you may apply for equal status with Danish citizens, if you fall within Section 2(2) of the Act on Integration of Aliens in Denmark:</string>
    <string name="educationSUBtn1">Go to MitID</string>
    <string name="educationSUBtn2">How do I apply for SU as a Ukrainian refugee?</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp1">What are the the required document to be included in the application?</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp11">1. Diploma/certificate in the original language for each qualification that you want to have assessed. If you have more than one higher education qualification (e.g. a bachelor’s degree and a master’s degree), please enclose all of the documents.</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp12">"  2. Transcript in the original language for each qualification that you want to have assessed. If you are unable to provide the transcript, please list in your own words the subjects studied and passed."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp13">"  3. Translation of the diploma/certificate for each qualification that you want to have assessed, unless it is in Norwegian, Swedish, English, German, French, or Spanish. If you attach a Diploma Supplement issued in one of the languages mentioned, translation is not necessary (see point 5)."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp14">"  4. Translation of transcript for each qualification that you want to have assessed, unless it is in Norwegian, Swedish, English, German, French, or Spanish. If you attach a Diploma Supplement issued in one of the languages mentioned, translation is not necessary (see point 5)."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp15">"  5. If you have a Diploma Supplement, please enclose it. The Diploma Supplement is issued by the higher education institutions in the EU/EEA countries."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp16">"  6. If you want assessment of a degree, please enclose the entrance qualification, e.g. high school certificate."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp17">"  7. If the name on any of the documents is different from the name you are currently using: Name change documentation, e.g. marriage certificate."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp18">"  8. If your qualifications have been assessed before: Former assessment(s) or recognition decision(s)."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp19">"   The Danish Agency for Higher Education and Science may ask you for further documentation of your qualifications, including original documents. "</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp2">How do I fill in the online application?</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp20">The form has five steps:</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp21">"  1. You as an applicant: Name, address etc. Most of the fields are filled in automatically."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp22">"  2. The purpose of your application. You will also be asked if you want the assessment in Danish or English. You can only get the assessment in one language. We recommend Danish if you are going to apply for jobs or education in Denmark."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp23">"  3. Education: Please give information about each of the education programmes that you have completed, except short programmes/courses."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp24">"  4. Other information, e.g. professional experience."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp25">"  5. Sending the application. Here you can check all of your information."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp26">"   When you have sent the application, you will get a receipt."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp3">How do I fill in the PDF application?</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp30">The form has four steps:</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp31">"  1. Fill in the application form. Fields marked * are required. "</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp32">"  2. Sign the form."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp33">"  3. Enclose all of the required documentation."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp34">"  4. Send the application, or hand it in at Haraldsgade 53, Copenhagen Ø."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp35">"   Letter post:"</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp36">" Send to: Danish Agency for Higher Education and Science, Haraldsgade 53, DK-2100 Copenhagen Ø."</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp37">"   Digital post:"</string>
    <string name="educationDiplomPopUp38">" If you have a Danish CPR number and NemID/MitID you can send your application by Digital Post, unless you are to submit original documents."</string>
    <string name="educatioOptionsPopUp1">How to apply for a transfer</string>
    <string name="educatioOptionsPopUp12">To apply for a transfer, it is required that you fulfil the general and specific admission requirements of the particular Danish higher education programme, and that there are available study places at the higher education programme.</string>
    <string name="educatioOptionsPopUp13">"  The higher education institutions in Denmark set their own procedures for applications for transfers, so you need to contact them directly in order to know more about the possibilities for a transfer. The individual higher education institution will also be able to guide you regarding ongoing higher education programmes at the institution."</string>
    <string name="educatioOptionsPopUp2">How do I apply for admission?</string>
    <string name="educatioOptionsPopUp22">If you haven’t passed the equivalent of the first year of a Danish higher education programme, you can apply for admission to the higher education programme in quota</string>
    <string name="educatioOptionsPopUp23">"  You can apply on https://www.optagelse.dk. Application deadlines are 15th of March every year. The higher education institutions have the option of giving a dispensation from application deadlines given unusual circumstances."</string>
    <string name="educatioOptionsPopUp24">"  In the 2022 admission round there are 12 English taught higher education programmes on an academy profession level or professional bachelor level, where Ukrainian applicants with an Ukrainian upper secondary diploma do not have to pass a test in order to be admitted."</string>
    <string name="educatioOptionsPopUp25">" If you want to apply for a bachelor’s programme and you have a Ukrainian upper secondary diploma, you must have passed at least one year of studies at a higher education programme besides your Ukrainian upper secondary education."</string>
    <string name="educatioSUPopUp1">How do I apply for SU as a Ukrainian refugee?</string>
    <string name="educatioSUPopUp12">If you are a refugee from Ukraine, you may apply for equal status with Danish citizens, if you fall within Section 2(2) of the Act on Integration of Aliens in Denmark</string>
    <string name="educatioSUPopUp13">"  Please be aware that if you want to apply for equal status with Danish citizens because you fall within Section 2(4) (other aliens granted family reunification) of the Act on Integration of Aliens in Denmark, you must have obtained the right to reside in Denmark according to this rule on 1 July 2019 or later."</string>

</resources>